<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<joke globalid="1052" localid="295" category="Dirty-Jokes" name="The Tiger" source="http://www.coolfunnyjokes.com/Funny-Jokes/Dirty-Jokes/The-Tiger.html">&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;td colspan="2"&gt; A couple was on their honeymoon, lying in bed, about ready to consummate their marriage, when the new bride says to the husband, "I have a confession to make, I'm not a virgin." &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The husband replies, "That's no big thing in this day and age." &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The wife continues, "Yeah, I've been with one guy." &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; "Oh yeah? Who was the guy?" &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; "Tiger Woods." &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; "Tiger Woods, the golfer?" &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; "Yeah." &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; "Well, he's rich, famous and handsome. I can see why you went to bed with him." &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The husband and wife then make passionate love. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; When they are done, the husband gets up and walks to the telephone. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; "What are you doing?" asks the wife. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The husband says, "I'm hungry, I was going to call room service and get something to eat." &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; "Tiger wouldn't do that." &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; "Oh yeah? What would Tiger do?" &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; "He'd come back to bed and do it a second time." &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The husband puts down the phone and goes back to bed to make love a second time. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; When they finish, he gets up and goes over to the phone. "Now what are you doing?" she asks. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The husband says, "I'm still hungry so I was going to get room service to get something to eat." &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; "Tiger wouldn't do that." &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; "Oh yeah? What would Tiger do?" &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; "He'd come back to bed and do it again." &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The guy slams down the phone, goes back to bed, and makes love one more time. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; When they finish he's tired and beat. He drags himself over to the phone and starts to dial. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The wife asks, "Are you calling room service?" &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; "No! I'm calling Tiger Woods, to find out what the par is for this damn hole." </joke>
