<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<joke globalid="1033" localid="276" category="Adult-Jokes" name="Jeff the Bellboy" source="http://www.coolfunnyjokes.com/Funny-Jokes/Adult-Jokes/Jeff-the-Bellboy.html">Bellboy &lt;/b&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;td colspan="2"&gt; Three couples got married and spent their honeymoons at the same hotel, where they were all attended to by Jeff the Bellboy. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The first man married a nurse. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Jeff showed them to their room, all the while thinking to himself, "Lucky guy! Nurses are known to be hot to trot." &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The second man married a telephone operator. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Jeff showed them to their room, while thinking to himself, "Wow, he's one lucky dude. Telephone operators have such sexy voices and once you pop that top button.. Va-voom." &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The third man married a school teacher. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Jeff showed them to their room and thought to himself, "Poor sap. She may be pretty, but teachers are way too frigid." &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; At 5:30 the following morning, Jeff reported to work. He expected the teacher's husband to call for breakfast any minute, but was sure the other two wouldn't call until much later in the day. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The phone rang at 6 a.m. and it was the nurse's husband wanting breakfast. Jeff took breakfast up to the room and when the husband opened the door, Jeff stepped back in shock. The man's pajamas were still pressed and his hair nicely combed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; "Sir, what happened?" asked Jeff. "You married a nurse." &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; "Son, don't ever marry a nurse," the man sourly replied. "All I heard last night was her nagging voice saying, 'You're not sanitary, you're not sanitary'." &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The phone rang again at 6:30 a.m. and this time it was the telephone operator's husband calling for breakfast. Jeff took it to the room as quickly as possible. When the man opened the door, Jeff stepped back in shock. The man's hair was neatly combed and his pajamas nicely pressed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; "What happened?" Jeff asked with surprise. "Telephone operators as supposed to be as sexy as their voices." &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; "Son, don't ever marry a telephone operator," the man groaned. "All I heard last night was her nasal voice saying, 'Your three minutes are up, your three minutes are up'." &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Jeff returned to his desk, sure that the teacher's husband would be calling at any moment. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Finally, at 4 p.m., the teacher's husband called for breakfast. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Jeff couldn't believe it, but quickly took the breakfast to the couple's room. When the man opened the door, Jeff stepped back in shock. The man was wearing only a pair of boxers, his hair was a mess, and there were scratches all over his chest, arms and legs. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; "My goodness sir, what happened to you?" Jeff asked, fearing the worst. "Did you have a fight?" &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The man, grinning from ear to ear, happily replied, "No. Son, when you marry be sure it's to a school teacher. All I heard last night was her sexy, smooth voice saying, 'We're going to do this over, and over, and over again, until we get it right'." </joke>
