<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<joke globalid="1054" localid="297" category="Computer-Jokes" name="New Viruses on the loose!" source="http://www.coolfunnyjokes.com/Funny-Jokes/Computer-Jokes/New-Viruses-on-the-loose!.html">on the loose! &lt;/b&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;td colspan="2"&gt; Oprah Winfrey virus: &lt;br /&gt; Your 200MB hard drive suddenly shrinks to 80MB and then slowly expands back to 200MB. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; AT&amp;T virus: &lt;br /&gt; Every three minutes it tells you what great service you are getting. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; MCI virus: &lt;br /&gt; Every three minutes it reminds you that you're paying too much for the AT&amp;T virus. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Politically Correct virus: &lt;br /&gt; Never calls itself a "virus", but instead refers to itself as an "electronic microorganism." &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Arnold Schwarzenegger virus: &lt;br /&gt; Terminates and stays resident. It'll be back. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Government Economist virus: &lt;br /&gt; Nothing works, but all your diagnostic software says everything is fine. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; New World Order virus: &lt;br /&gt; Probably harmless, but it makes a lot of people really mad just thinking about it. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Federal Bureaucrat virus: &lt;br /&gt; Divides your hard disk into hundreds of little units, each of which does practically nothing, but all of which claim to be the most important part of your computer. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Texas virus: &lt;br /&gt; Makes sure that it's bigger than any other file. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Adam and Eve virus: &lt;br /&gt; Takes a couple of bytes out of your Apple. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Congressional virus: &lt;br /&gt; The computer locks up, screen splits erratically with a message appearing on each half blaming the other side for the problem. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Airline virus: &lt;br /&gt; You're in Dallas but your data is in Singapore. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Freudian virus: &lt;br /&gt; Your computer becomes obsessed with marrying to its own motherboard. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Public Television virus: &lt;br /&gt; Your programs stop every few minutes to ask for money. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Elvis virus: &lt;br /&gt; Your computer gets fat, slow and lazy, then self destructs only to resurface at shopping malls and service stations across rural America. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Nike virus: &lt;br /&gt; Just does it. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Congressional virus #2: &lt;br /&gt; Runs every program on the hard drive simultaneously, but doesn't allow the user to accomplish anything. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Star Trek virus: &lt;br /&gt; Invades your system in places where no virus has gone before. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Health Care virus: &lt;br /&gt; Tests your system for a day, finds nothing wrong, and sends you a bill for $4,500. &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; </joke>
